[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
PlayResX: 1280
PlayResY: 720

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Last Style Storage: Toji no Miko
Audio File: C:/torrents/[Ohys-Raws] Toji no Miko - 04 (AT-X 1280x720 x264 AAC).mp4
Video File: C:/torrents/[Ohys-Raws] Toji no Miko - 04 (AT-X 1280x720 x264 AAC).mp4
Video AR Mode: 4
Video AR Value: 1.777778
Video Zoom Percent: 0.750000
Scroll Position: 349
Active Line: 356

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Episode Title,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,13,13,27,1
Style: Screen,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,13,13,27,1
Style: Reference,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,13,13,27,1
Style: OP_JP,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1
Style: OP_CN,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1
Style: ED_JP,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1
Style: ED_CN,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.95,0:00:02.58,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉 只能送你到这儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.40,0:00:05.05,Default,,0,0,0,,在这里放了我？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.74,0:00:07.87,Default,,0,0,0,,也不能再带着你乱转啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.95,0:00:12.59,Default,,0,0,0,,你的 拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.16,0:00:14.57,Default,,0,0,0,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.03,0:00:18.44,Default,,0,0,0,,想动手的就拔刀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.61,0:00:25.46,Default,,0,0,0,,小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.96,0:00:27.32,Default,,0,0,0,,再见 沙耶加
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.73,0:00:37.59,Default,,0,0,0,,商量好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.68,0:00:39.24,Default,,0,0,0,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.43,0:00:42.51,Default,,0,0,0,,碰头地点是定了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.56,0:00:45.26,Default,,0,0,0,,我还是不多问了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.56,0:00:48.06,Screen,,0,0,0,,##这是？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.56,0:00:48.06,Screen,,0,0,0,,##碰头地点
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.84,0:00:47.60,Default,,0,0,0,,那个软件也删了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.73,0:00:52.46,Default,,0,0,0,,现在我家那边肯定闹翻了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.68,0:00:55.84,Default,,0,0,0,,这辆车可能也被盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.32,0:00:59.26,Default,,0,0,0,,有个叫N系统的东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.99,0:01:01.40,Default,,0,0,0,,糟了 有路卡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.26,0:01:04.60,Default,,0,0,0,,就在这里下车吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.47,0:01:09.48,Default,,0,0,0,,累小姐 承蒙您照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.86,0:01:11.27,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起 还没好好道谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.54,0:01:12.64,Default,,0,0,0,,没事 快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.25,0:01:14.10,Default,,0,0,0,,有机会再见
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.63,0:01:18.62,Default,,0,0,0,,之后应该会很辛苦 加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.66,0:01:21.66,Default,,0,0,0,,要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.69,0:01:23.10,Default,,0,0,0,,伊豆
Comment: 0,0:01:32.98,0:03:02.91,Default,,0,0,0,,OP
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.29,0:03:17.02,Default,,0,0,0,,阳光明媚 可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.00,0:03:21.43,Episode Title,,0,0,0,,##第4集 决心之重
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.78,0:03:21.67,Default,,0,0,0,,现在来海边还是有点早了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.71,0:03:28.94,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.32,0:03:31.00,Default,,0,0,0,,薰要不要一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.29,0:03:32.56,Default,,0,0,0,,不了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.82,0:03:35.26,Default,,0,0,0,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.76,0:03:37.47,Default,,0,0,0,,有任务？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.80,0:03:38.70,Default,,0,0,0,,好突然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.45,0:03:41.69,Default,,0,0,0,,不管 就说放假勿扰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.39,0:03:44.83,Default,,0,0,0,,她说「不管 放假勿扰」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.14,0:03:49.01,Default,,0,0,0,,薰 再说一句试试
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.13,0:03:53.42,Default,,0,0,0,,可让我执行任务 手头也没有祢祢切丸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.03,0:03:56.15,Default,,0,0,0,,昨天才发快递寄出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.68,0:03:57.76,Default,,0,0,0,,我给你送回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.60,0:04:10.16,Default,,0,0,0,,纳税人的钱都花哪儿去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.21,0:04:20.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你有斩杀她的决心吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.32,0:04:21.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我不会砍下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.52,0:04:31.78,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢您送我们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.46,0:04:33.20,Default,,0,0,0,,十分感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.25,0:04:41.07,Default,,0,0,0,,还挺累人的 你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.54,0:04:43.24,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.24,0:04:44.72,Default,,0,0,0,,可奈美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.11,0:04:45.58,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.43,0:04:49.61,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你帮了我这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.64,0:04:52.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我们还是在这里分手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.77,0:04:56.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我说过 会和你在一起的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.54,0:04:59.70,Default,,0,0,0,,不能继续下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.73,0:05:01.80,Default,,0,0,0,,不能再和你一起走下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.89,0:05:03.60,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.81,0:05:06.36,Default,,0,0,0,,经历了昨晚的事 我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.99,0:05:09.41,Default,,0,0,0,,我的剑和你的剑不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.13,0:05:11.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我用剑来斩杀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.81,0:05:13.39,Default,,0,0,0,,而你用剑来守护
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.44,0:05:16.29,Default,,0,0,0,,接下来的路 只需要斩杀的剑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.34,0:05:19.03,Default,,0,0,0,,不要替我做决定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.80,0:05:21.67,Default,,0,0,0,,只是姬和想多了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.80,0:05:26.80,Default,,0,0,0,,可奈美 你斩杀过真正的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.73,0:05:30.87,Default,,0,0,0,,不是假身的？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.59,0:05:34.34,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯 或者是变成荒魂的人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.66,0:05:36.94,Default,,0,0,0,,没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.36,0:05:41.86,Default,,0,0,0,,近些年 几乎不再有人类变成荒魂的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.00,0:05:43.97,Default,,0,0,0,,但在不久之前
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.10,0:05:48.99,Default,,0,0,0,,特别是我妈妈那一辈人 还是经常遇上的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.33,0:05:52.82,Default,,0,0,0,,变成荒魂的人 就不是人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.83,0:05:56.72,Default,,0,0,0,,偶尔有保留记忆 能够说话的例子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.25,0:05:58.48,Default,,0,0,0,,但荒魂就是荒魂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.43,0:06:03.16,Default,,0,0,0,,只能用御刀斩杀祓除 没有别的办法可以拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.48,0:06:08.48,Default,,0,0,0,,我们刀使是替人们背负祖先的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.87,0:06:10.36,Default,,0,0,0,,扫除一切荒魂的巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.34,0:06:15.15,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.09,0:06:19.41,Default,,0,0,0,,接下来我要做的 是消灭荒魂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.99,0:06:21.86,Default,,0,0,0,,但几乎就是杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.57,0:06:27.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我要斩杀折神紫 还有挡在我面前的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.40,0:06:30.72,Default,,0,0,0,,而且我的动机十分接近私人恩怨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.13,0:06:33.60,Default,,0,0,0,,可你做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.60,0:06:36.08,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我们该分手了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.37,0:06:38.84,Default,,0,0,0,,等下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.70,0:06:42.41,Default,,0,0,0,,一点杀气都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.04,0:06:49.03,Default,,0,0,0,,你回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.69,0:06:51.57,Default,,0,0,0,,回去 从荒魂手中保护人们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.17,0:06:59.52,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起 柴田先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.17,0:07:01.44,Default,,0,0,0,,让您费心了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.45,0:07:05.71,Default,,0,0,0,,嗯 请转告父亲 不要担心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.23,0:07:08.39,Default,,0,0,0,,还有妈妈 美结 诗织
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.68,0:07:12.59,Default,,0,0,0,,柳濑同学打算在这里留多久
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.20,0:07:15.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我校的羽岛校长在这里的期间 我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.10,0:07:17.04,Default,,0,0,0,,岩仓同学呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.67,0:07:19.20,Default,,0,0,0,,我今天就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.79,0:07:20.88,Default,,0,0,0,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.56,0:07:24.40,Default,,0,0,0,,还是想和十条同学一起回去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.41,0:07:27.22,Default,,0,0,0,,毕竟是一起来这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.28,0:07:29.94,Default,,0,0,0,,沙耶加
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.26,0:07:35.75,Default,,0,0,0,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.08,0:07:41.30,Default,,0,0,0,,她是镰府的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.06,0:07:42.76,Default,,0,0,0,,丝见同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.49,0:07:50.10,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么搞的 还让辖区部队收留你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.18,0:07:53.45,Default,,0,0,0,,十分…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.58,0:07:57.40,Default,,0,0,0,,找到了敌人的位置 发动奇袭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.40,0:07:59.84,Default,,0,0,0,,结果失手了 还腆着脸回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.74,0:08:03.61,Default,,0,0,0,,看来之前太高看你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.58,0:08:07.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我对无聊的御前比武没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.11,0:08:13.44,Default,,0,0,0,,但是 百分百完成任务才是你存在的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.52,0:08:17.60,Default,,0,0,0,,是不是对你太娇生惯养了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.29,0:08:21.22,Default,,0,0,0,,门没锁
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.44,0:08:24.18,Default,,0,0,0,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.26,0:08:27.32,Default,,0,0,0,,紫大人让我带您过去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.36,0:08:29.32,Default,,0,0,0,,紫大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.53,0:08:32.37,Default,,0,0,0,,镰府校长
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.03,0:08:33.92,Default,,0,0,0,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.77,0:08:36.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我不记得允许过你去追击
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.60,0:08:39.78,Default,,0,0,0,,因为确定了叛徒的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.24,0:08:43.57,Default,,0,0,0,,我想不需劳烦您出手 按自己的判断…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.92,0:08:45.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我决不容忍擅自行动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.53,0:08:48.85,Default,,0,0,0,,但是我咽不下这口气
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.42,0:08:51.68,Default,,0,0,0,,不能让对紫大人以刀相向的逆贼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.77,0:08:54.05,Default,,0,0,0,,在触手可及的地方逍遥自在
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.80,0:08:57.10,Default,,0,0,0,,您为什么不交给我解决
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.80,0:09:00.62,Default,,0,0,0,,高津校长 注意言辞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.05,0:09:01.66,Default,,0,0,0,,黄毛丫头
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.73,0:09:03.15,Default,,0,0,0,,雪那
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.83,0:09:04.28,Default,,0,0,0,,在…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.81,0:09:07.20,Default,,0,0,0,,你先做好该做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.74,0:09:08.66,Default,,0,0,0,,紫大人？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.72,0:09:10.91,Default,,0,0,0,,够了 退下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.75,0:09:21.02,Default,,0,0,0,,夜见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.36,0:09:32.72,Default,,0,0,0,,准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.38,0:09:34.08,Default,,0,0,0,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.30,0:09:39.44,Default,,0,0,0,,那么…Mission Start
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.67,0:09:51.02,Default,,0,0,0,,找到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.65,0:09:58.63,Default,,0,0,0,,美浓关学院初中二年级
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.87,0:10:00.36,Default,,0,0,0,,卫藤可奈美 没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.21,0:10:02.07,Default,,0,0,0,,是我没错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.19,0:10:06.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我是长船女子学园高中一年级
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.08,0:10:08.30,Default,,0,0,0,,古波藏艾伦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.91,0:10:12.18,Default,,0,0,0,,然后这位是薰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.48,0:10:18.37,Default,,0,0,0,,大胆狂徒 竟敢对折神家家主以刀相向
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.67,0:10:19.93,Default,,0,0,0,,准备受死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.63,0:10:23.87,Default,,0,0,0,,话说回来 十条姬和在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.74,0:10:26.16,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和不在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.72,0:10:28.22,Default,,0,0,0,,但是如果你们要去追姬和的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.53,0:10:29.57,Default,,0,0,0,,就由我来当你们的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.38,0:10:31.68,Default,,0,0,0,,那就好说了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.95,0:10:36.26,Default,,0,0,0,,真他妈麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.76,0:10:39.12,Default,,0,0,0,,药丸自显流
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.71,0:10:40.40,Default,,0,0,0,,嗷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.32,0:10:44.81,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.47,0:10:48.47,Default,,0,0,0,,好强的威力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.23,0:10:50.46,Default,,0,0,0,,啧 让她躲开了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.07,0:10:51.86,Default,,0,0,0,,真麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.12,0:10:54.16,Default,,0,0,0,,要是敢接就能直接拍扁她了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.59,0:10:57.38,Default,,0,0,0,,金刚身？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.18,0:11:06.93,Default,,0,0,0,,用金刚身的体舍流和体术？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.92,0:11:16.10,Default,,0,0,0,,面对她不能拉开距离
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.58,0:11:17.69,Default,,0,0,0,,必须近身
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.31,0:11:22.84,Default,,0,0,0,,这样根本近不了身
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.46,0:11:25.32,Default,,0,0,0,,这两个人 像合为一体了一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.20,0:11:26.49,Default,,0,0,0,,糟了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.62,0:11:28.05,Default,,0,0,0,,太好了 抓住了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.47,0:11:29.38,Default,,0,0,0,,就是现在 薰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.32,0:11:37.01,Default,,0,0,0,,好危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.76,0:11:39.13,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和 为什么回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.48,0:11:40.79,Default,,0,0,0,,你才是 为什么不逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.29,0:11:41.80,Default,,0,0,0,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.84,0:11:45.07,Default,,0,0,0,,这下终于变成二对二了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.59,0:11:52.00,Default,,0,0,0,,嗷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.93,0:11:56.38,Default,,0,0,0,,不行 这两个人的配合得太完美了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.10,0:12:03.16,Default,,0,0,0,,薰和我可是最佳搭档
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.97,0:12:04.49,Default,,0,0,0,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.59,0:12:12.08,Default,,0,0,0,,只要避开第一击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.27,0:12:18.54,Default,,0,0,0,,什么 荒魂？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.79,0:12:22.40,Default,,0,0,0,,对 你眼神不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.86,0:12:24.17,Default,,0,0,0,,这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.81,0:12:30.33,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然上次的比试输给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.00,0:12:32.57,Default,,0,0,0,,这次可说不好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.12,0:12:39.11,Default,,0,0,0,,这种招数…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.19,0:12:43.02,Default,,0,0,0,,毕竟在比武里用会挨骂的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.89,0:12:48.50,Default,,0,0,0,,受死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.97,0:13:08.87,Default,,0,0,0,,这次是长船的刺客吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.72,0:13:11.01,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么知道我们在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.13,0:13:14.61,Default,,0,0,0,,保密
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.76,0:13:19.09,Default,,0,0,0,,什么 荒魂？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.83,0:13:21.67,Default,,0,0,0,,好像是听她指挥的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.42,0:13:23.84,Default,,0,0,0,,驱使荒魂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.81,0:13:25.88,Default,,0,0,0,,回答我的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.45,0:13:27.22,Default,,0,0,0,,否则…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.05,0:13:28.74,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.37,0:13:31.06,Default,,0,0,0,,我要达成我的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.44,0:13:32.53,Default,,0,0,0,,碍我者斩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.33,0:13:34.89,Default,,0,0,0,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.40,0:13:36.51,Default,,0,0,0,,终于肯开口了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.14,0:13:40.65,Default,,0,0,0,,那个 麻烦再等一下 5秒左右
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.25,0:13:42.08,Default,,0,0,0,,5秒？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.10,0:13:50.75,Default,,0,0,0,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.67,0:13:52.52,Default,,0,0,0,,S装备
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.13,0:13:54.75,Default,,0,0,0,,用来歼灭荒魂的装备
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.32,0:13:59.02,Default,,0,0,0,,S装备？我只在实习时穿过一次
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.66,0:14:00.26,Default,,0,0,0,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.33,0:14:04.38,Default,,0,0,0,,重装上阵
Comment: 0,0:14:04.85,0:14:06.94,Default,,0,0,0,,<Armored Kaoru>
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.85,0:14:06.94,Default,,0,0,0,,装甲薰<Armored Kaoru>登场
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.32,0:14:11.36,Default,,0,0,0,,这样形势就逆转了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.08,0:14:12.79,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.30,0:14:14.92,Default,,0,0,0,,准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.40,0:14:16.48,Default,,0,0,0,,一 二…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.71,0:14:24.16,Default,,0,0,0,,喂 接下来不是主角机大杀特杀吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.07,0:14:30.43,Default,,0,0,0,,镰府的人跟我撤离
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.20,0:14:32.33,Default,,0,0,0,,不再插手这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.19,0:14:36.04,Default,,0,0,0,,到头来没能帮上一点忙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.54,0:14:38.88,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.55,0:14:41.10,Default,,0,0,0,,横须贺基地问我们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.85,0:14:45.27,Default,,0,0,0,,是不是往南伊豆的山上发射了S装备
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.99,0:14:46.83,Default,,0,0,0,,S装备？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.73,0:14:49.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我没收到过任何报告
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.54,0:14:51.63,Default,,0,0,0,,请看影像
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.91,0:14:57.60,Default,,0,0,0,,确实像是发射舱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.52,0:14:59.56,Default,,0,0,0,,撤离延期了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.32,0:15:02.49,Default,,0,0,0,,找出那东西精确的着陆点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.84,0:15:07.67,Default,,0,0,0,,狮童小姐 此花小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.66,0:15:10.77,Default,,0,0,0,,紫大人下达了出击命令
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.88,0:15:12.86,Default,,0,0,0,,请准备一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.10,0:15:19.14,Default,,0,0,0,,没追上来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.48,0:15:22.29,Default,,0,0,0,,那是还在开发中的特殊装备
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.09,0:15:24.98,Default,,0,0,0,,使用时间应该有限制
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.72,0:15:29.84,Default,,0,0,0,,又下雨了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.05,0:15:32.28,Default,,0,0,0,,看来会下大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.41,0:15:41.93,Default,,0,0,0,,拖到现在才派我们出动
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.25,0:15:44.77,Default,,0,0,0,,紫大人也真会故弄玄虚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.89,0:15:48.76,Default,,0,0,0,,真少见 没想到你会离开紫大人身边
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.88,0:15:52.36,Default,,0,0,0,,我的能力能协助侦察敌情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.31,0:15:54.63,Default,,0,0,0,,结芽留下来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.39,0:15:58.33,Default,,0,0,0,,把她放出去的话 会有不必要的流血发生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.69,0:16:02.82,Default,,0,0,0,,无聊得要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.82,0:16:03.69,Default,,0,0,0,,也对
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.85,0:16:06.99,Default,,0,0,0,,不过怎么可能呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.98,0:16:11.05,Default,,0,0,0,,居然还有不受折神家管辖的S装备
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.27,0:16:13.95,Default,,0,0,0,,除了折神家和管理局
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.44,0:16:16.58,Default,,0,0,0,,没有能开发运用S装备的组织
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.61,0:16:18.95,Default,,0,0,0,,如果真的有 那只可能是在管理局内…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.72,0:16:21.97,Default,,0,0,0,,是说之前的「舞草」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.85,0:16:24.16,Default,,0,0,0,,如果那群人像传闻所说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.49,0:16:26.68,Default,,0,0,0,,是特祭队内部的造反分子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.13,0:16:27.90,Default,,0,0,0,,那这事也并非没有可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.75,0:16:34.13,Default,,0,0,0,,紫大人猜到十条姬和一行会与其有接触 欲擒故纵
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.96,0:16:36.79,Default,,0,0,0,,可能是这么回事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.44,0:16:44.87,Default,,0,0,0,,你觉得她们怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.72,0:16:47.94,Default,,0,0,0,,能力没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.79,0:16:50.08,Default,,0,0,0,,其他的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.23,0:16:52.90,Default,,0,0,0,,薰怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.19,0:16:56.33,Default,,0,0,0,,感觉不是简单的愣头青
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.65,0:17:08.72,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你来救我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.39,0:17:17.09,Default,,0,0,0,,刚刚接下姬和那一剑的时候 我就感受到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.12,0:17:20.90,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和的剑很沉重
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.50,0:17:25.46,Default,,0,0,0,,要是论对敌人的杀伤力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:28.42,Default,,0,0,0,,昨晚沙耶香的剑更胜一筹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.96,0:17:32.33,Default,,0,0,0,,威力的话 刚刚拿大太刀的那位更厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.74,0:17:36.98,Default,,0,0,0,,但是姬和的剑却是最沉重的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.22,0:17:39.16,Default,,0,0,0,,到底想说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.28,0:17:43.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我觉得你的剑上承载着意志
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.01,0:17:47.67,Default,,0,0,0,,想要达成目标的强烈意志
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.76,0:17:49.69,Default,,0,0,0,,所以才这样沉重
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.99,0:17:55.96,Default,,0,0,0,,那时候…殿前比武的决赛上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.96,0:18:00.89,Default,,0,0,0,,我光想着姬和会怎样攻过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.70,0:18:04.04,Default,,0,0,0,,心里装的全是你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.15,0:18:08.93,Default,,0,0,0,,但是姬和眼里根本没有我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.56,0:18:13.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我那时候好生气的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.36,0:18:14.98,Default,,0,0,0,,生气？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.92,0:18:18.68,Default,,0,0,0,,因为被你无视了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.74,0:18:27.16,Default,,0,0,0,,还有如果那时不出手 姬和会被杀掉这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.96,0:18:32.30,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和说得没错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.60,0:18:34.26,Default,,0,0,0,,我没有决心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.75,0:18:36.26,Default,,0,0,0,,也没有想做到什么的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.28,0:18:38.96,Default,,0,0,0,,但现在我能说出这句话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.66,0:18:42.46,Default,,0,0,0,,如果我的剑是用来守护的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.02,0:18:46.14,Default,,0,0,0,,那我选择保护你和你的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.36,0:18:50.64,Default,,0,0,0,,那到头来就是杀人犯的帮凶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.64,0:18:51.45,Default,,0,0,0,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.89,0:18:55.92,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和要斩杀的是家主…不
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.46,0:18:58.17,Default,,0,0,0,,是化为人形的荒魂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.98,0:19:00.73,Default,,0,0,0,,除此之外的一切 我都不会让你斩杀的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.76,0:19:03.28,Default,,0,0,0,,这就是我的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.02,0:19:11.43,Default,,0,0,0,,我要打倒折神紫的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.99,0:19:15.72,Default,,0,0,0,,之前不是讲等我想说的时候再说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.61,0:19:17.25,Default,,0,0,0,,那我现在告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.93,0:19:25.90,Default,,0,0,0,,可奈美 你知道20年前发生的大荒魂事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.85,0:19:28.82,Default,,0,0,0,,相模湾大灾难？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.20,0:19:33.34,Default,,0,0,0,,在江之岛出现了史上最可怕的大荒魂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.80,0:19:38.91,Default,,0,0,0,,折神紫大人和现任五传的校长组成特攻队将其消灭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.79,0:19:41.34,Default,,0,0,0,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.10,0:19:45.57,Default,,0,0,0,,而我的母亲也是那个特攻队的一员
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.83,0:19:49.31,Default,,0,0,0,,但没有留下任何的记录
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.06,0:19:50.86,Default,,0,0,0,,这也是当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.63,0:19:55.54,Default,,0,0,0,,人所共知的那套事件经过全是编造的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.63,0:19:57.45,Default,,0,0,0,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.42,0:20:02.65,Default,,0,0,0,,所有的真相都写在这封信里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.67,0:20:09.23,Default,,0,0,0,,你看到的东西…英雄折神紫的真实身份…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.97,0:20:15.83,Default,,0,0,0,,正是那人们口中被讨伐了的大荒魂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.77,0:20:22.92,Default,,0,0,0,,是能威胁到这个国家…不 威胁世界存亡的灾害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.62,0:20:26.91,Default,,0,0,0,,可憎之物 完全纯粹的污秽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.98,0:20:28.76,Default,,0,0,0,,这就是它的真实身份
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.66,0:20:31.96,Default,,0,0,0,,而众多刀使之中
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.96,0:20:36.19,Default,,0,0,0,,唯一有能消灭它的力量的 就是我的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.31,0:20:39.80,Default,,0,0,0,,姬和的母亲？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.91,0:20:43.18,Default,,0,0,0,,但却没能完全歼灭它
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.45,0:20:47.02,Default,,0,0,0,,它化身成折神紫活了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.69,0:20:51.84,Default,,0,0,0,,而用尽刀使力量的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.42,0:20:54.40,Default,,0,0,0,,却眼见着一年年越来越衰弱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.48,0:20:59.21,Default,,0,0,0,,去年她在我面前过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.09,0:21:03.07,Default,,0,0,0,,那天晚上我便发誓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.84,0:21:11.73,Default,,0,0,0,,夺走母亲的生命 却仍然潜藏在人世的恶魔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.15,0:21:13.23,Default,,0,0,0,,就由我亲手了结
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.30,0:21:17.15,Default,,0,0,0,,我要完成母亲未竟的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.22,0:21:27.01,Default,,0,0,0,,你所说的沉重 有一半是身为刀使的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.12,0:21:29.62,Default,,0,0,0,,但另一半只是我的私人恩怨
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.05,0:21:32.64,Default,,0,0,0,,所以你不需要陪着我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.74,0:21:35.64,Default,,0,0,0,,这样啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.70,0:21:43.73,Default,,0,0,0,,这么沉重的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.14,0:21:45.47,Default,,0,0,0,,就让我来分担一半吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.90,0:22:02.25,Default,,0,0,0,,雨正好也停了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.43,0:22:05.74,Default,,0,0,0,,开始搜山
Comment: 0,0:22:15.25,0:23:44.54,Default,,0,0,0,,ED
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.98,0:23:49.99,Episode Title,,0,0,0,,下集 搜山之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.00,0:00:07.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Comment: 0,0:01:31.28,0:01:32.95,Default,,0,0,0,,【OP】
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.21,0:01:35.64,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,すべてを薙ぎ払えるような
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.64,0:01:38.18,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,すべてを守り抜けるような
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.18,0:01:41.32,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,そんな未来を見ていた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.07,0:01:55.68,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,考える暇もなくて歩いていく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.98,0:02:01.04,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,夢はいつも見えるようで見えないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.15,0:02:05.97,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,どうすればいいかなんてもうわかっていた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.08,0:02:11.28,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,目の前にある壁　壊していくだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.11,0:02:16.91,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,偶然の証明　必然の運命
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.17,0:02:22.95,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,ただ見ている真実さえ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.80,0:02:26.03,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,切先が指した方へ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.22,0:02:28.71,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,すべてを薙ぎ払えるように
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.71,0:02:31.24,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,すべてを守り抜けるように
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.36,0:02:34.09,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,息を止めて　振りかざす
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.21,0:02:36.07,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,一筋に光って
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.24,0:02:38.92,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,諦めたくない思いとか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.92,0:02:41.88,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,悔しくてたまらないことも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.95,0:02:43.94,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,この胸に刻む
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.94,0:02:46.95,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,これからの糧にしてもう一回だ！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.95,0:02:52.51,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,まだまだまだまだ止まんないから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.00,0:02:59.74,OP_JP,,0,0,0,,全てを守り抜くよ　ここから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:11.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.00,0:00:13.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.00,0:00:15.00,Default,,0,0,0,,【ED】
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.56,0:22:21.02,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,Let's hang out
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.64,0:22:25.58,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,I wanna talk with you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.81,0:22:29.61,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,待ち合わせは何時？（10時）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.84,0:22:31.77,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,駅前に集合（OK！）
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.88,0:22:35.36,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,着いたら教えて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.48,0:22:37.29,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,使い慣れたスタンプで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.54,0:22:39.92,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,話合えちゃうスタンスが本当
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.12,0:22:43.65,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,心地良くて愛しい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.17,0:22:47.72,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,一人胸にしまいこんだ言葉も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.32,0:22:51.95,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,上手くいかない減らない悩み事も
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.34,0:22:58.39,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,全部忘れて遊びに行きたいね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.81,0:23:04.89,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,心のメモリア
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.89,0:23:07.98,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,笑顔が溢れるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.28,0:23:12.17,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,冗談混じりで頷く
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.39,0:23:16.12,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,何気ないありふれたやり取りが
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.26,0:23:21.32,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,心のメモリア
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.32,0:23:24.42,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,涙が零れても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.71,0:23:26.91,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,頑張れるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.91,0:23:33.56,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,君がくれた今日が優しくてありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.45,0:23:34.90,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,Let's hang out
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.49,0:23:39.34,ED_JP,,0,0,0,,I wanna talk with you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:17.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
