[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2018-01-06 00:22:05
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1
Style: Episode Title,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,13,13,27,1
Style: Screen,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,13,13,27,1
Style: Reference,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,13,13,27,1
Style: Default_JP,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,48,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.53,0:00:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.03,0:00:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是「刀使」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.22,0:00:11.09,Screen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,**斩！相信这一刻的情感
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.53,0:00:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了从可怕的荒魂手中保护大家
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.82,0:00:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都在战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.48,0:00:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都战斗 每天！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.18,0:00:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要求休假
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.58,0:00:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别挑我字眼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刀使巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.25,0:00:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,播送时间如上
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.53,0:00:01.03,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.03,0:00:02.53,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私たちは「刀使」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.22,0:00:11.09,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怖い荒魂からみんなを守るために
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.53,0:00:04.82,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毎日戦ってマース
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.82,0:00:06.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毎日戦う　毎日！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.48,0:00:08.18,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休みを要求する
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.18,0:00:09.58,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言葉の綾デスヨ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.58,0:00:11.23,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「刀使ノ巫女」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.23,0:00:12.25,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ご覧の時間に放送中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:02.15,Screen,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,**解说：益子薰&古波藏艾伦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
