[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2017-01-29 22:55:04
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Default Aegisub file
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭黑_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.96,0:00:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸出你的手来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.52,0:00:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.34,0:00:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,属于我的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.81,0:00:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺特…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.90,0:00:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧尔菲…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.93,0:00:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥汀…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.70,0:00:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗雷托尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.28,0:00:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪耀弧光箭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.33,0:00:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.37,0:01:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪亮之杖 我没有做梦呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.82,0:01:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终于来到了魔女学校露娜诺瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.58,0:01:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 耶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.40,0:01:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 洛蒂 你瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.39,0:01:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是闪亮之杖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.25,0:01:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答对了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.52,0:01:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你昨晚都问过不下百回了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.54,0:01:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪亮夏莉欧的魔法杖
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.57,0:01:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道为什么会在那个树林里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.81,0:01:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我会保管到见到夏莉欧的那一天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.58,0:01:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了这根魔杖 我觉得自己什么魔法都能使出来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.99,0:01:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,床呀 飞起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.02,0:02:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来 阿尔克鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.10,0:02:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快动快动 给我动起来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.17,0:02:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 动一动嘛 你这坏蛋 动啊动啊动啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.78,0:02:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 快动一动嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.36,0:02:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 为什么就是不动呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.62,0:02:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 我肯定…肯定做得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.49,0:02:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 我行的 我可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.74,0:02:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 喝 看这招
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.95,0:02:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 怎么样 还没完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.67,0:02:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 喝 再来一次 嘿 喝 哈
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.75,0:02:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苏西你在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.31,0:02:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从石化鸡蛇的羽毛里提取石化毒素
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.91,0:02:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得你会上露娜诺瓦 就是为了收集猛毒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.22,0:02:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来准备得到石化鸡蛇的羽毛就回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.41,0:02:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但听说这所学校有灭绝的毒蘑菇的标本
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.90,0:02:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就多在这里待一阵子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.81,0:02:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风啊 刮起来吧 将脸颊都吹裂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.81,0:02:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪啊 昨天明明放出魔法来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.99,0:02:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点换换衣服吧 上课要迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.11,0:03:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上课？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.37,0:03:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶 变身完毕 在下就此出阵
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.84,0:03:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是办仪式做实习时穿的 平时上课要穿这身
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.47,0:03:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.57,0:03:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一节课是魔法语言学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.04,0:03:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后是基础魔药学 魔法数秘学
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.05,0:03:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天起 我就将迈出成为魔女的第一步
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.06,0:03:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚可 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.73,0:03:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.46,0:04:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【OP】
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.58,0:04:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【只改一句】
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.58,0:04:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,変わらないまま時間の光見つめて歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.58,0:04:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遥望那永恒不变的时光而踏上旅程
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.00,0:05:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 露娜诺瓦第1598次新学期的课程开始之际
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.05,0:05:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们向古代的大魔女 九长者献上敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.51,0:05:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娥苏拉老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.42,0:05:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.02,0:05:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请打起点精神来 娥苏拉老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.68,0:05:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样还怎么给学生做表率
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.74,0:05:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.17,0:05:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.42,0:05:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 究竟是怎么回事呢 娥苏拉老师
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.96,0:05:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你想要辅导新生亚可·卡嘉莉？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.47,0:06:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算抽空 私下教教卡嘉莉同学魔法的基础
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.00,0:06:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且在各方面多照顾她一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.41,0:06:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是非魔女家系的日本学生 第一次走进露娜诺瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.56,0:06:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定有不少不知所措的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.45,0:06:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是对一直都拿不出教师威严的你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.22,0:06:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感到不知如何是好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.68,0:06:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是卡嘉莉同学
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.81,0:06:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,芬纳兰老师 那我先去跟她打声招呼…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.86,0:06:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 哎呀哎呀哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.24,0:06:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有点土啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.50,0:06:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 不知道魔法课是什么样子的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.07,0:06:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好期待好兴奋呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.94,0:06:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说 露娜文字是远古的魔女们使用的古文字体系
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.98,0:07:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可以说是音素文字的一种
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.91,0:07:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能把黑板上的字给念出来？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.09,0:07:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡文迪许小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.35,0:07:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不动石则福分将至 动石者则大难临头
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.81,0:07:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,念得太好了 戴安娜·卡文迪许
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.45,0:07:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我当上老师起 只有你能念出这段文字
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.02,0:07:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安娜果然非同小可
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.79,0:07:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不停地搅动 颜色就会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.10,0:07:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再把活青蛙放入大釜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.46,0:07:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青蛙必须摆在水里放进去 这样才能收集汁液
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.05,0:07:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上蝾螈的肠子 蝙蝠爪的精粉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.96,0:07:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这些一点 一点地加进去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.00,0:07:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 味道开始好闻了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.74,0:08:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就…就像我刚才说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.16,0:08:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法与占卜体系的基础 据说是由毕达哥拉斯建立的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.69,0:08:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 请看第923页102行所写的内容
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.37,0:08:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在数秘学上 宇宙由1到5来表示…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.49,0:08:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴德考克老师
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.18,0:08:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是从1到5 而是从1到4吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.41,0:08:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我竟然会犯这种错误…你说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.08,0:08:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴德考克的老脸都没地方搁咯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.80,0:08:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样 魔法课怎么会这么无聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.78,0:09:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满梦想呀奇迹呀 而闪亮亮的才是魔法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.04,0:09:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 洛蒂 帮我拿下那个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.33,0:09:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 哦 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.03,0:09:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉跟想象的不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.03,0:09:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信闪亮夏莉欧是在这所学校学的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.21,0:09:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本没有人认可闪亮夏丽欧的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.26,0:09:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少在这所学校里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.45,0:09:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是叫卡嘉莉吧 新来的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.86,0:09:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝我哈科够行…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.76,0:09:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我亚可就行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.08,0:09:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是课上特别显眼的那位…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.70,0:09:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安娜·卡文迪许
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.68,0:09:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然连戴安娜都不认识吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.14,0:09:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在魔法界可是超有名的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.48,0:09:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都说她会是露娜诺瓦有史以来最强的魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.37,0:09:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我就称呼你为亚可吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.52,0:09:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在魔法界 没有人会高度评价夏莉欧的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.15,0:09:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请你记住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.75,0:09:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.46,0:09:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏莉欧的魔法表演享誉全世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.70,0:09:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前人气可好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.28,0:10:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实 她曾在世间红极一时
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.13,0:10:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 只是外表华丽讨喜的魔法不可能一直行得通
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.77,0:10:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏莉欧离开魔法表演舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.40,0:10:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,销声匿迹已经快十年了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.09,0:10:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在根本没有人想知道她在哪 又在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.19,0:10:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏莉欧她…给了我梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.36,0:10:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是真的 我还找到了闪亮之杖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.49,0:10:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪亮之杖？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.21,0:10:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随处都能见到的赝品吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.96,0:10:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.60,0:10:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种玩具也拿来炫耀吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.88,0:10:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还挺符合麻瓜的身份呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.45,0:10:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让你们看看 夏莉欧的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.41,0:11:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.71,0:11:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了 亚可
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.23,0:11:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以做到的 心怀坚信就一定可以
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.35,0:11:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 闪亮之杖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.81,0:11:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像昨天一样引起奇迹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.18,0:11:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动起来吧 石像
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.24,0:11:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石像啊 动起来 快动起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.57,0:11:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到没 快动起来 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.30,0:11:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你动起来呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.00,0:11:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚可
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.19,0:11:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 昨天明明…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.25,0:11:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安索尔 艾洛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.17,0:12:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 好厉害 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.90,0:12:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是赋予石像生命的高等魔法？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.74,0:12:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安娜才是奇迹的魔女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.97,0:12:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚可 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.79,0:12:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法 是在漫长传统和不懈钻研中孕育而成的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一时追求时髦的人 是学不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.57,0:12:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安娜出生于有1500年底蕴的名门 卡文迪许家族
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.53,0:12:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和夏莉欧这种艺人魔女有本质上的区别
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.93,0:12:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 戴安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.29,0:13:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娥苏拉老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.60,0:13:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.48,0:13:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才拜托的事情 你帮我调查了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.92,0:13:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我这就去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.97,0:13:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 阿尔克鲁 这只星辰之兽，会听从光芒闪耀的人的话。闪亮之杖承认的人呼唤它的话，它会跨越银河与时空的界限而出现。\N0:13:26.97--0:13:29.68
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.22,0:13:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚信的心灵就是你的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.64,0:13:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,销声匿迹已经快十年了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.71,0:13:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏莉欧现在在哪做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.33,0:13:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像确实没人知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.50,0:13:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.22,0:13:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 这些卡全部集齐很费劲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.04,0:13:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 小时候正是夏莉欧热潮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.98,0:14:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都热衷于收集卡片
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.81,0:14:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 闪亮之杖 向天际挥舞这把魔杖，便会有光芒集聚形成太阳与月亮。也会有满溢的水滴流淌出银河与满天星光。\N 0:14:15.81--0:14:19.81
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.11,0:14:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 坚信的心灵就是你的魔法 七星的光之魔法。漫游在光之海的七种身姿。\N 0:14:28.11--0:14:30.11
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.30,0:14:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚信的心灵就是你的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.84,0:14:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这一张特殊卡是我没有得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.84,0:14:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时想要得不得了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.49,0:14:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唤醒恋心的蘑菇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.73,0:14:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是独角兽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.33,0:14:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守护少女幸福的永恒圣兽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.05,0:14:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你都背下来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.65,0:14:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然全记下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.90,0:15:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然对咒语的发音没什么信心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.52,0:15:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个我知道 魔法蝴蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.58,0:15:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展凤蝶（papiliodya）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.22,0:15:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在五大洲迁徙生活的蝴蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.77,0:15:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,120年羽化一次
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.17,0:15:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说会为见到的人心中点亮希望
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.36,0:15:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是衰弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.22,0:15:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厄休拉老师 你查出原因了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.10,0:15:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 失去活力应该只是暂时的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.70,0:15:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要消除了根本问题…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.87,0:15:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本问题？你有没有查出什么情报
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.64,0:15:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还需要进一步的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.16,0:15:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先仔细查清楚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.38,0:15:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校长 珍妮弗纪念树竟然会如此虚弱…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.86,0:15:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 戴安娜 这棵树的年纪已经很大了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.76,0:15:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定是大寿将近了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.64,0:16:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珍妮弗纪念树
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.65,0:16:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说继承了大魔女珍妮弗的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.53,0:16:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是露娜诺瓦的生命之树
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.73,0:16:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这边完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.93,0:16:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试试给这棵魔法树施活化术
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.28,0:16:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给大型植物输送浓烈养分 使之起死回生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.90,0:16:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们卡文迪许家代代相传的秘术
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.00,0:16:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛佩里欧·拉尔！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.26,0:16:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,养分应该已经充满了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.60,0:16:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害 戴安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.23,0:16:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉老师们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.30,0:17:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 就是这个了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.42,0:17:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么一直都没想到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.78,0:17:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 奇迹已经走近了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.84,0:17:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给苏西的生命造成4点伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.36,0:17:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说 我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.21,0:17:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶 九连胜
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.97,0:17:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么卡片上没写的事你都能做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.89,0:17:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.18,0:17:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再来一局
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.42,0:17:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.22,0:17:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 亚可
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.17,0:17:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这究竟是？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.63,0:17:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快离开
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.42,0:18:00.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安娜…到底发生了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.75,0:18:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.29,0:18:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.69,0:18:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是蛹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.33,0:18:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛹？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.55,0:18:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还不是普通的蛹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.73,0:18:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来树根上有寄生虫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.63,0:18:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以纪念树才会衰弱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.13,0:18:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的魔法把营养送给了害虫 而不是纪念树
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.33,0:18:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须驱除
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.97,0:18:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆拉瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.36,0:18:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆拉瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.16,0:18:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆拉瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.74,0:18:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.82,0:18:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆拉…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.10,0:18:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 戴安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.29,0:18:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能不是害虫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.11,0:18:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别碍事 快让开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.79,0:18:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不让
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.89,0:18:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姆拉瓦！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.12,0:19:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚可！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.33,0:19:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.98,0:19:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你犯什么傻！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.10,0:19:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法在全身波动剧烈 这下糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.93,0:19:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展凤蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.62,0:19:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是展凤蝶的蛹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.25,0:19:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.04,0:19:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 120年羽化一次的展凤蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.44,0:19:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会为见到的人心中点亮希望的魔法蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.98,0:19:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 亚可 来咏唱这个咒语吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.51,0:20:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展凤蝶的咒语…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.28,0:20:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想想…帕皮里欧·费路亚…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.11,0:20:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是帕皮里欧·费里欧·尼弗迪亚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.26,0:20:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是正确的发音吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.62,0:20:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.76,0:20:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跨越五大洲的展凤蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.36,0:20:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒展双翅吧 魔法蝶哟 向着希望
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.23,0:20:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕皮里欧·费里欧·尼弗迪亚！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.71,0:21:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展凤蝶会在阴暗的地下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.16,0:21:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经历120年的幼虫时期后破蛹成蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.84,0:21:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成蝶之际 她们欢快翱翔的身影…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.43,0:21:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.54,0:21:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们欢快翱翔的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.54,0:21:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会为见到的人心中点亮希望
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.31,0:21:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纪念树已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.53,0:21:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.10,0:21:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了戴安娜的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.82,0:21:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 戴安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.02,0:21:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 这不是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.66,0:21:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了你 还有谁能做到这种事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.99,0:21:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.94,0:21:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我失礼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.46,0:21:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安娜才是露娜诺瓦的骄傲
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.08,0:22:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【ED】
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.92,0:22:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢中になって追いかけてた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.54,0:22:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流れ星辿った先に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.70,0:22:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,広がる世界を知りたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.08,0:23:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶えたいと　願うだけじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.72,0:23:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扉を開ければ　ほら
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.70,0:23:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近づいて行けるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.86,0:23:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待ちきれない物語の続きを探そう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.38,0:23:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未来信じられるのは一人じゃないから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.44,0:23:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,景色は変わっていくけど　輝く空と
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.05,0:23:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巡りあった宝物　いつまでも離さないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.96,0:23:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう　泣いて笑って食べて寝ても
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.08,0:23:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くよくよしちゃいそうなときでも
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.56,0:23:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そばにいてくれてありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.88,0:23:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また明日ね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.92,0:22:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘我地追逐着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.54,0:22:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流星滑落的彼方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.70,0:22:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只因想见识广阔的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.08,0:23:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别仅仅埋头企盼愿望成真
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.72,0:23:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推开房门 你瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.70,0:23:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈开双脚 就能接近梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.86,0:23:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐不住了 起身寻找故事的后续
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.38,0:23:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有勇气相信未来的可不只是你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.44,0:23:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路风景千变万化 但灿烂天辉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.05,0:23:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及寻觅到的宝物 却从不曾离开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.96,0:23:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论哭着笑着吃着睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.08,0:23:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕是有烦恼不开心的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.56,0:23:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也要谢谢你陪在我的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.88,0:23:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就明天见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
