[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2017-01-17 00:27:47
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 漫游字幕
Original Script: 漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正兰亭黑_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,30,30,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.98,0:00:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到魔法之国
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.98,0:00:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸出你的手来 属于你的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.53,0:00:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.84,0:01:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺特 欧尔菲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.77,0:01:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥汀 弗雷托尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.65,0:01:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪耀弧光箭（Shiny Arc）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.94,0:02:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘记 坚信的心灵就是你的魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.38,0:02:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 小魔女学园
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.81,0:02:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.55,0:02:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界第一魔女 闪亮夏莉欧曾经学习的圣地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.05,0:03:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要在这里成为魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.93,0:03:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 你好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.88,0:03:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问到露娜诺瓦的巴士站在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.05,0:03:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那位闪亮夏丽欧上的学校
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.73,0:03:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道哪里可以搭巴士去露娜诺瓦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.14,0:03:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂你们知道吗 这附近有个巴士站吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.92,0:03:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个镇子上都没有巴士站呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.12,0:03:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.97,0:03:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里应该有个车站的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.68,0:03:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这张地图也太粗枝大叶了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.25,0:03:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁看得懂这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.24,0:04:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到啦找到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.36,0:04:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.93,0:04:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.16,0:04:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的吗 你是露娜诺瓦的新生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.26,0:04:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正准备去参加开学典礼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.43,0:04:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 要我一个人走进魔女学园
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.00,0:04:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实还有一点害怕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.01,0:04:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫亚可 6岁时看了闪亮夏丽欧的魔法表演
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就一直梦想成为魔女了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.52,0:04:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直不只是梦想而是宿命了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.02,0:04:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定也知道闪亮夏丽欧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.49,0:04:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 夏莉欧的稀有卡 我的宝贝喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.33,0:04:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在魔法界 夏莉欧也很了不起吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.64,0:04:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我身边一个喜欢她的人都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.94,0:05:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总是说我「还在讲那么早的事啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.83,0:05:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也只有夏莉欧 才能做到那么厉害的事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.97,0:05:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟她把月亮都…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.64,0:05:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 是傀儡魔法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.46,0:05:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是头一次亲眼见到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.99,0:05:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖 来姐姐的手里 别害怕哟
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.59,0:05:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来快来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.13,0:05:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛 眼睛…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.25,0:05:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你过分了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.14,0:05:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.31,0:05:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字 刚刚是怎么做到的呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.27,0:05:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也念过网购来的魔法教材 但完全不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.13,0:05:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连自己的基础做得如何都不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.71,0:05:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过等我进了学园
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.29,0:05:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许就能用夏莉欧用的魔法了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.19,0:05:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.58,0:06:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.38,0:06:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌讨厌讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.04,0:06:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了 那家伙是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.18,0:06:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露娜诺瓦的校服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.62,0:06:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春假怎么过的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.31,0:06:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪儿都全是游客 烦死了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.40,0:06:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说今天来参加开学典礼的新生中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.78,0:06:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说有一个不是出身魔女家庭的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.09,0:06:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.18,0:06:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 最近招的麻瓜太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.23,0:06:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近学校经营困难
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.24,0:06:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算不是魔女家庭出身的学园也得招了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.37,0:06:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟透了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.35,0:07:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露娜诺瓦的格调都要掉光了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.18,0:07:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定连扫帚都不会骑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.30,0:07:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.23,0:07:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扫帚都不会骑的魔女
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.11,0:07:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在露娜诺瓦的历史上从未出现过喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.13,0:07:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.36,0:07:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚可·卡嘉莉 就是新生中的…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.02,0:07:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.00,0:07:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…但愿巴士能早点到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.93,0:07:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴士？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.79,0:07:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是巴士站吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.85,0:07:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是啥都不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.44,0:07:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为这里会有巴士来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.40,0:07:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提亚 芙琉涅
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.14,0:07:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是扫帚休息站
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.09,0:07:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵脉始发站
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.49,0:07:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵脉连接着露娜诺瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.61,0:07:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从远古时期起 魔法能量就在灵脉上奔流
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.85,0:07:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搭上这股能量 就能一跃飞向露娜诺瓦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.64,0:07:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这正是魔法的高速公路
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.55,0:07:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是魔法基础知识喔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.31,0:08:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.99,0:08:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开学典礼迟到的话 会被魔法界永久除名的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.11,0:08:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.86,0:08:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要迟到了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.72,0:08:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 老妈和雅姐她们让我带太多特产了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.69,0:08:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.17,0:09:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提亚 芙琉…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.41,0:09:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不走吗 开学典礼要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.64,0:09:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没见过你呢 是新生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.09,0:09:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露娜诺瓦校规很严的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.41,0:09:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迟到的话就进不了学校了 会被立刻劝退
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.23,0:09:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有扫帚 再说有也不会骑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.44,0:09:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 但我要迟到了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.66,0:09:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.86,0:09:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然没试过两个人骑 但试一下或许能做到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.20,0:09:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.33,0:09:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是有热心肠的魔女呀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.38,0:09:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是亚可·卡嘉莉 叫我亚可就好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.46,0:09:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫洛蒂 快点吧 已经没时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.77,0:09:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.17,0:09:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就出发吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.91,0:09:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.02,0:09:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞翔吧 我的扫帚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.82,0:09:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提亚 芙琉涅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.15,0:10:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧不会吧 飞起来了飞起来了飞起来了飞…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.65,0:10:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是行李太重了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.52,0:10:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开吧 通向露娜诺瓦的路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.47,0:10:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事怎么回事怎么回事怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.59,0:10:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行不行啊 放我下去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.91,0:10:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你稍微老实点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.45,0:10:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带的东西…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.07,0:10:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说之森阿尔克图拉斯 一般的魔女无法进入
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.83,0:10:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么一片黑…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.17,0:10:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情况还是第一次 太奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.02,0:10:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你身上带了盐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.66,0:10:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盐？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.07,0:10:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灵脉厌恶盐分
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.80,0:11:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是这个？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.29,0:11:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.42,0:11:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅干
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.49,0:11:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快丢掉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.73,0:11:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有梅干就活不下…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.17,0:11:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 快丢掉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.24,0:11:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.85,0:11:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.13,0:11:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 危险
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.72,0:11:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.84,0:11:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.89,0:11:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 阿鲁克尔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.26,0:12:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是去了阿尔克图拉斯森林？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.24,0:12:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.62,0:12:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好啦 我的宝贝还在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.51,0:12:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死掉了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.09,0:12:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所谓烦人至极 说的就是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.87,0:12:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.49,0:12:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点程度魔女还死不了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.25,0:12:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛蒂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.88,0:12:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 有没有受伤？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.45,0:12:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事 但扫帚…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.73,0:12:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我是到目的地了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.17,0:12:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的地？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.14,0:12:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这里就是露娜诺瓦咯 开学典礼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.29,0:12:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 这里是我不认识的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.58,0:13:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔克图拉斯森林
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.35,0:13:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔克图拉斯…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.29,0:13:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧 禁忌之森？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.28,0:13:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.98,0:13:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一片古老传说中的森林
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.90,0:13:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被魔法树庇佑的神圣之地
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.94,0:13:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说一旦在里面迷路 就算是魔女也很难出去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.46,0:13:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也太糟了 要赶不上开学典礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.22,0:13:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何止啊 说不定一生都走不出这里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.52,0:13:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别这么吓人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.01,0:13:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到弄丢的行李了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.73,0:13:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚可 快离开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.55,0:13:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.13,0:13:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.93,0:14:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是曼达拉草 有毒植物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.64,0:14:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.70,0:14:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.85,0:14:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.14,0:14:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.47,0:14:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.09,0:14:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.10,0:14:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站那儿别动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.72,0:14:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约纳斯 哈纳斯 哈纳斯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.52,0:14:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.84,0:14:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我念咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.70,0:14:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咒语？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.79,0:14:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以找到路吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.63,0:14:46.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库裘鲁 卡特拉 弗拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.65,0:14:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库裘鲁卡特 弗…弗拉弗拉？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.20,0:14:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库裘鲁 卡特拉 弗拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.35,0:14:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再大点声音念！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.55,0:14:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库裘鲁 卡特拉 弗拉拉！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.03,0:15:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.28,0:15:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.57,0:15:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么 刚才的咒语是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.97,0:15:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是「蠢货 不服就来吃掉我啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.56,0:15:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是只存在于阿尔克图拉斯森林的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.41,0:15:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说中的石化鸡蛇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.10,0:15:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说羽毛上含有剧毒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.47,0:15:40.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对剧毒收藏家来说可是超稀有道具呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.28,0:15:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们去引开它的注意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.14,0:15:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会趁机取它的羽毛的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.88,0:15:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说让我们去当诱饵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.92,0:15:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错了 是祭品 再念一遍刚才的咒语
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.93,0:15:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会念啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.57,0:15:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对就是这样 小心点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.06,0:16:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是沾上它的吐息 就会变石头的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.16,0:16:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.09,0:16:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.27,0:16:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢厚赐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.09,0:16:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停…停不下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.66,0:16:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.15,0:16:42.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.21,0:16:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得抓紧时间
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.98,0:16:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,磨磨蹭蹭的就要赶不上开学典礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.97,0:16:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.61,0:16:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的腿…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.37,0:16:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 赶不上的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.46,0:16:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.36,0:16:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会放弃的 绝对！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.16,0:17:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要去！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.59,0:17:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要成为魔女！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.62,0:17:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伸出你的手来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.10,0:17:13.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会开始
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.84,0:17:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忐忑不安 却又叫人激动的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.38,0:17:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,属于我的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.16,0:17:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…夏莉欧的魔杖
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.68,0:17:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洛蒂 躲起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.82,0:17:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库裘鲁 卡特拉 弗拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.03,0:18:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖魔鬼怪 看这边 我鼓掌的这边
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.03,0:18:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,# 一句日本传统童谣的歌词
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.49,0:18:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.00,0:18:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.70,0:18:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.43,0:18:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.33,0:18:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苏西 苏西·曼巴巴兰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.09,0:18:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 苏西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.45,0:19:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死缠烂打的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.83,0:19:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三个人坐一把扫帚跑不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.57,0:19:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.37,0:19:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下居然喷火了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.37,0:19:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么她们会在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.63,0:19:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 烧起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.33,0:19:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…闪亮之杖
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.41,0:19:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫烫烫烫
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.68,0:19:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,张开嘴巴！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.68,0:19:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,念出咒语！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.41,0:19:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔杖…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.91,0:19:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺特 欧尔菲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.42,0:19:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺特 欧尔菲…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.74,0:19:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥汀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.45,0:19:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥汀…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.58,0:19:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗雷托尔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.14,0:20:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪耀 弧光箭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.54,0:20:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位同学 假期过得还开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.89,0:20:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这培养出了众多伟大魔女的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.43,0:20:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,历史悠久的我校
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.82,0:21:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位同学今天起将再度
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.66,0:21:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心怀骄傲与礼貌 同时不忘谦虚地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.43,0:21:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专心致志于魔法的学习之中
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.74,0:21:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么开学典礼正式开…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.65,0:21:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.68,0:21:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.35,0:21:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赶上了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.05,0:21:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.95,0:21:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 简直是前所未闻的开学典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.61,0:21:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能入学 要多亏校长对你网开一面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.07,0:21:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切记不可忘记这份恩情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.24,0:21:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.90,0:22:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向室友打声招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.23,0:22:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今天起的三年间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.83,0:22:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们三个会受到格外严格的教导吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.77,0:22:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是亚可·卡嘉莉 请多关照
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.63,0:22:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【OP】
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.75,0:22:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駆け出した日々に　行き着いたこの場所
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.32,0:22:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触れた扉　開いて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.23,0:22:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星空の彼方　夢の足跡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.77,0:23:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拾い集め　歌うよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.68,0:23:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢がかけてく場所　今も心に秘めて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.56,0:23:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜を包み込む
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.81,0:23:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法をかけて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.88,0:23:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踊り出す
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.70,0:23:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,焼き付いたように色づいた風景は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.97,0:23:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,転んだくらいじゃ解けないから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.14,0:23:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界は続くよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.70,0:23:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儚いままの今を抱きしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.44,0:23:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,変わらないまま時間の光見つめて歩いてく
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.75,0:22:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑出家门的日子 总会来到这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.32,0:22:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻轻推开门扉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.23,0:22:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是星空的彼端 洒满了梦的足迹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.77,0:23:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会唱着歌 将它们拾起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.68,0:23:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依然藏在心中的 这片缀织梦的场所
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.56,0:23:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笼罩着迷人的夜色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.81,0:23:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吟唱魔法
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.88,0:23:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳起舞步
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.70,0:23:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧这片令人心醉 五彩缤纷的美景
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.97,0:23:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚在地上可是看不到的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.14,0:23:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万物流转不息
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.70,0:23:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我怀抱稍纵即逝的这一刻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.44,0:23:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,踏上寻找永恒不变的时光的旅程
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【ED】
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
