If days were not the same
I don’t know what I’d do
Imagine me laughing and now
See me walk in the street
Then catch a red double bus
And heaven would find me
I’d go on a float
Eased up, I smile a dream
Now you know
There is a scene that I…
I repeat in my soul
While slippin’ a black tea, and now
Gently touching a tree
Calming hi-beam from the sky
Can free me, I feel like
I’m getting so close
to laughing sweet with everything
(Goin’ out on)
Sunday morning, the light has come
(La la, morning the light’s on me…)
And looking up high
(Looking around, you’ll see all around)
Vanish worries the light has come
(La la, shining the light on me…)
I’m going to try for a pleasant “now”
Just a page of life in my story
Sweet and bright